{
    "id": "41be201eb85e485aa3151fa78f890a87",
    "title": "Parts Of Speech Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I have never had a better experience. Here 'never' is a/an .....................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "adjective",
                "adverb",
                "verb",
                "preposition"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "She has always been a nuisance. Here nuisance is a/an ...................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "adjective",
                "adverb",
                "noun",
                "preposition"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "I am tired of listening to his stupid instructions. Here stupid is a/an ...................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "adjective",
                "adverb",
                "verb",
                "noun"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I am hoping to get a raise this year. Here 'this' is a/an ...................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "pronoun",
                "noun",
                "adjective",
                "adverb"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "To watch him eating really gets on my nerves. Here 'gets' is a/an .......................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "pronoun",
                "adjective",
                "verb",
                "adverb"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "It is nice to be sitting here with you. Here 'here' is a/an .........................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "adjective",
                "adverb",
                "verb",
                "pronoun"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "In spite of having a headache I enjoyed the movie. Here 'in spite of' is a/an ..................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "adjective",
                "conjunction",
                "preposition",
                "verb"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "He came to Chicago to look for work. Here 'work' is a/an .......................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "preposition",
                "noun",
                "verb",
                "conjunction"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "There is a bus stop in front of the school. Here 'in front of' is a/an ......................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "conjunction",
                "preposition",
                "verb",
                "noun"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "He was driving very fast indeed. Here 'was driving' is a/an ...................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "verb",
                "noun",
                "adverb",
                "conjunction"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "She sat facing me across the table. Here 'across' is a/an ....................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "conjunction",
                "preposition",
                "adjective",
                "adverb"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I made them give me my money back. Here 'them' is a .....................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "noun",
                "pronoun",
                "conjunction",
                "preposition"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        }
    ]
}